Guide to the Manuel Ruiz Papers, 1931-1986
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES IV: ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, 1931-1977
  - Subseries B: Coordinating Council for Latin American Youth, 1941-1948
    - Ephemera (mostly business cards) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Financial records, 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Membership records, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings, 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Police, CCLAY and community relations, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Postwar Planning Congress, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Programs, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Resolutions, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Rosters and ballots, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Social clubs, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Subseries C: Other Organizations, 1931-1956
    - California Committee on Youth in Wartime, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - California Committee on Youth in Wartime 1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - California Youth Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - California Youth Committee, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Circulo Mexicano, 1940-1943 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Citizens' Committee for Latin American Youth 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Comite de Beneficencia Mexicana, 1931-1946 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Comite Pro-Damnificados de Mazatlan, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles County Committee for Interracial Progress, 1943-1946 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles County Committee on Human Relations, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles County Coordinating Council Excutive Board, 1942-1947 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Los Angeles Youth Project, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Los Angeles Youth Project, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Mexican Athletic Association (and other amateur athletic groups), 1937-1944 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Mexican Businessmen's Cooperative, 1945-1947 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Mexican Chamber of Commerce of Los Angeles, 1943-1953 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Museum of Immigration, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Pan-American Trade School, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - President's Committee of Fair Employment Practice, 1941-1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Public Education Human Relations Committee, Los Angeles City Schools, 1948-1951 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Public Education Human Relations Committee, Los Angeles City Schools 1952 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Southern California Council of Inter-American Affairs, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Southern California Inter-American Council, 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Statewide Committee for a California Fair Employment Practices Commission, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Constitutions, By-laws and Articles of Incorporation, miscellaneous groups, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Membership lists, miscellaneous groups, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Programs, miscellaneous groups, 1940s (1) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Programs, miscellaneous groups, 1940s (2) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D: Mexican American Political Organization, 1962-1977
    - State Level, California
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Balance sheets, Sept., 1968-July, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Bracero issue, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Brown, Governor Edmund G., meetings with MAPA 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Brown, Governor Edmund G., meetings with MAPA, speeches and testimony, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - By-laws/State Constitution, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - By-laws/State Constitution, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - By-laws/State Constitution, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - By-laws/State Constitution, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - By-laws/State Constitution, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - By-laws/State Constitution, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - By-laws/State Constitution, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - By-laws/State Constitution, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - California Department of Employment meetings with House of Representatives Committee on Education and Labor, July, 1965; June, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Civil rights, 1964-1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Convention, Annual, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Convention, Annual, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Convention, Annual, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Convention, Annual, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Convention, Annual, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Convention, Annual, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Convention, Endorsing, National, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Convention, Endorsing, National and State, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Convention, Endorsing, State, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Coordinating Council for Hispanic-American Unity, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, internal, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, internal, 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Executive Board, meeting announcement, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Executive Board, meetings, June, July, Dec., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Executive Board, meetings, Apr., Oct., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Executive Board, meetings, May, June, Sept., Dec., 1966 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Executive Board, meetings, Feb., May, June, July, Oct., Dec., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Executive Board, meetings, Jan., Apr., May, June, July, Sept., Nov., Dec., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Grant application, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Legal Committee, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Meetings (unidentified), 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Mexican-American Legislative Conference, Mar., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Mexican-American Study Project, UCLA, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Newsclippings, 1963-1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Officers' installation, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Open Resolution to the President of the United States on Civil Disobedience and Riot Investigations, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Rosters, state and regional officers, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Statement on the Delano Strike, Nov., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Women's Council, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - The Voice of the Spanish-Speaking People, accounts payable, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - The Voice of the Spanish-Speaking People, accounts receivable, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - The Voice of the Spanish-Speaking People, correspondence, general, Dec., 1965-Mar., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - The Voice of the Spanish-Speaking People, correspondence, general, Apr. 1966-Mar. 1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - The Voice of the Spanish-Speaking People, financial records, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - "La Voz de MAPA" (newsletter), 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Miscellany, 1961-1972 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Subseries E: Mexican American Political Association, 1964-1973
    - State Level, New Mexico
      - New Mexico MAPA, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Regional Level
      - Northern Region, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Southern Region, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Chapter Level
      - By-laws, model for chapters, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Chapters, Blythe, Coachella Valley, Compton, Corona (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Chapters, Fremont, Fresno, Hanford (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Chapters, Los Angeles, 40th Assembly District, 1966-1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Chapters, Los Angeles, "Illume" (newsletter), 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Chapters, Los Angeles County, 41st Assembly District, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Chapters, Monterey, Napa, National City (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Chapters, Oakland, Pico Rivera (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Chapters, Roseville, Sacramento-East Yolo, San Bernardino, San Francisco (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Chapters, San Jose, Sonoma, Ventura County, West Valley (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Rosters, Bakersfield-Escondido (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Rosters, Fremont-Irwindale (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Rosters, Los Angeles-National City (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Rosters, Oakland-Redlands (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Rosters, Richmond-San Jose (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Rosters, San Luis Obispo-Woodland (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Rosters, Unassigned location (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - (for additional MAPA materials, see Box 22)
  - Subseries F: War On Poverty, Inc., 1965-1968
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors, correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors, minutes, Mar. 1965-June 1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors, minutes, July 1966-Jan. 1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors, rosters, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - By-laws, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Contract between War on Poverty, Inc., and the United States Department of Labor, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and contracts between War on Poverty, Inc., and the Economic and Youth Opportunities Agency of Greater Los Angeles, Mar.-Dec. 1966 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and contracts between War on Poverty, Inc., and the Economic and Youth Opportunities Agency of Greater Los Angeles, Jan.-June 1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and contracts between War on Poverty, July, 1967-July 1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - EYOA, Joint Powers Agreement, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - EYOA, "The War Against Poverty in Los Angeles," 1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Financial records, audit, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Financial records, quarterly tax returns, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Financial records, quarterly tax returns, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Financial records, statement of financial condition, June-Dec. 1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Grant application, Community Action Program 1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Grant application, Community Action Program, Exhibits 1-5 (background information), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Grant application, Community Action Program, Exhibit 6-8 (maps), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Grant application, Community Action Program, Exhibit 9 (resumes), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Grant application, Community Action Program, Exhibits 10-11 (staffing plan), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Grant application, Community Action Program, letters of support, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Unemployment insurance, California state, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Miscellany, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Accounting memoranda, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Audits, 1966-1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Community conference component, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Equipment inventories, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Funding, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Funding requests, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Funding requests, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Insurance, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Local share receipts, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Monthly financial reports and invoices, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Personnel file, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Program director, search for, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Progress reports, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Progress reports, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Proposals and contracts, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Proposals and contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Rodriguez, Jose M., program director, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Miscellany, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - (for additional ERIS material, see Box 22)
  - Subseries G: Manpower Opportunities Project, 1966-1971
    - General
      - Audit, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Closing out contract, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Feb. 1966-Jan 1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Feb.-July 1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Aug. 1967-Mar. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Funding extension, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - In-service training, Dec. 1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Newsletter, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - On-the-job training programs, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Project activities, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Project activities, Feb.-Apr. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Project activities, May-Nov. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Referrals to Job Corps, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Miscellany, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles Area Office
      - Correspondence and memoranda, May-Aug. 1966 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, Sept.-Dec. 1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, Jan.-Apr. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, May-Oct. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Minutes of staff meetings, Jan.-Aug. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Monthly reports, Jan.-Aug. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Weekly staff reports, Carlos, Christopher (Director), Dec. 1966-June 1967 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Weekly staff reports, Cordova, Sam, Jan.-Aug. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Weekly staff reports, Sanchez, Waldo, Jan.-Aug. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Weekly staff reports, Varela, Robert, Jan.-July, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Weekly staff reports, Orange County, Gonzalez, Fidel, Dec. 1966-June 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Weekly staff reports, Riverside and Imperial Counties, Lozano, Bernie, Feb.-Aug. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Weekly staff reports, San Bernardino and Riverside Counties, Vidaurri, Marina, Apr.-June 1967 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Weekly staff reports, San Diego County, Machado, Bill, Feb.-Mar. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - (for additional MOP material, see Box 22)
  - Subseries H: Other Organizations, 1964-1969
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission, 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Youth Opportunities Foundation, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- SERIES V: SUBJECT FILES
  - Subseries A: Civil Rights, 1933-1957
    - Delinquency, reports on, 1938-1943 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Diana Ballroom incident, notes, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Legislation, miscellaneous, 1943-1945 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Politics, miscellaneous, 1942-1947 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Racial discrimination and school segregation, 1936-1945 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Racial discrimination and school segregation, 1946-1948 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Lagoon Murder Case, Zoot Suit Riots, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Sleepy Lagoon Murder Case, and juvenile delinquency, newsclippings, 1942-1944 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Miscellany, 1933; 1940-1943 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Miscellany, 1944-1949 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Miscellany, 1951-1957 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Miscellany, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Mexican Americans and Education
    - Bilingual Education, newsclippings, 1966-1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Bilingual Education, printed information, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1968-1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., California Mini-Corps, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., 1967-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., Migrant Education Stanford Project, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., newsclippings, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., relations with Arizona State University, 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., relations with University of Southern California, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., versus California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo, 1974-1977 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Guerra, Manuel H., versus California Polytechnic State University 1975, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - School desegregation, newsclippings, 1970-1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, and education, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, and education, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, Bilingual Education Kit, ca. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, hearings on school desegregation, Boston, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, hearings on school desegregation, Denver, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, school desegregation, 1970-1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Subseries C: Police-Community Relations, 1967-1978
    - Commission on Human Relations, Law Enforcement and Police-Community Relations Committees, Los Angeles County, minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Newsclippings, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Newsclippings, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Salazar, Ruben, correspondence and notes concerning death of, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Salazar, Ruben, newsclippings concerning death of, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Salazar, Ruben, statement by Manuel Ruiz concerning death of, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Salazar, Ruben, writings, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, Police-Community Relations in East Los Angeles," 1970 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters and printed matter, 1970-1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous reports, reprints and flyers, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Administration of Justice, 1969-1978
    - Bilingual Courts Act, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Campos Torres, Jose, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Mexican-American Self Help Group, McNeil Island Federal Penitentiary, Washington, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Mexican-American Self Help Group, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - National Prison Project, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - National Prison Project, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Prison inmates, correspondence with, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Prison inmates, correspondence with, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Prisons, miscellany, 1970-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, Mexican Americans and the Administration of Justice in the Southwest" (summary); correspondence concerning the report, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, Mexican Americans and the Administration of Justice in the Southwest" (summary); newsclippings concerning the report, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, miscellany, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, miscellany, 1973-1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - United States Senate Bills and Legislative Testimony; S.B. 2963, 2964, "Criminal Justice Information Control," 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Subseries E: Miscellaneous Subjects, 1962-1977
    - Cabinet Committee on Mexican American Affairs, hearings, Oct. 1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Migrant workers, 1967-1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - United States Senate, Sub-committee to Investigate the Administration of the Internal Security Act and Other Internal Security Laws of the Committee on the Judiciary, "Extent of Subversion in the `New Left,'" 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters and printed matter, 1962-1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Miscellany, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Miscellany, 1970s (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Miscellany, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 9)
- SERIES VI: PHOTOGRAPHS
  - People (three include Manuel Ruiz, Jr.), 1968, 1972, 1977, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles Public Library, (removed from Box 2, Folder 6) ca. 1940 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- SERIES VII: OVERSIZED MATERIALS
  - Educational Resource Information Service, general ledger, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lopez, J. Robert, candidate for Assembly, 40th District (Los Angeles), paste-up of campaign advertisement 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Manpower Opportunities Project, general ledger, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Mexican American Political Association, Certificate of Merit, Los Angeles, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Mexican American Political Association, paste-up of campaign advertisement n.d. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Mexican American Political Association, pins (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Mexican American Political Association, The Voice of the Spanish-Speaking People, paste-up sheets for Vol. l, no. 5, pp. 1-4 Feb. 17, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Mexican American Political Association, Vol. 1, no. 7, Mar. 1, 1966, pp. 1-8 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Mexican American Political Association, proofs, Vol. 1, no. 12, May 19, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "Open Resolution Directed to the President of the United States and Executive Departments and Agencies, by National Hispanic and Mexican-American Organizations on Civil Disobedience and Riot Investigations," n.d. (Box 21, Folder 10)